PM
oh, it's okay
ああ、大丈夫です
I think it's very late
とても遅いと思います
I fucking depressed
落ち込んでいます
oh, wait, I hope it's okay
ああ、待って、大丈夫だといいのですが
how many hours do you enjoy sweet?
甘い時間は何時間楽しんでいますか？
ah, yeah
ああ、ええ
there is, there is
ある、ある
I don't know
わからない
and secondfully, I don't know
そして第二に、私は知りません
sometimes I get maybe eight hours, sometimes I get four hours
時々私は多分8時間を得るかもしれません、時々私は4時間を得る
four hours, oh, and it depends
4時間、ああ、それは依存します
yeah
うん
today, let's see, six
今日は、6人を見てみましょう
oh, not, oh, maybe I'll get
ああ、そうではありません、ああ、多分私は得るでしょう
not too much
多すぎない
not too much, you should be
あまりにも多くないはずです
no, I can't enough
いいえ、私は十分ではありません
you should, you should sleep more
あなたはもっと眠るべきです
did you have any dinner?
夕食はありましたか？
you can't tell me to sleep
あなたは私に眠るように言うことができません
I didn't tell you to stay here
私はあなたにここにとどまるように言いませんでした
yeah, exactly
ええ、まさに
I wanna talk with you
私はあなたと話したいです
yay
わーい
you kinda just thought
あなたはちょっと考えました
I was annoyed
私はイライラしました
yeah
うん
don't eat and then do the
食べないで、それをします
one, one, one, one
1つ、1つ、1つ、1つ
like I just randomly add comments
コメントをランダムに追加するように
goddess, you're going nuts
女神、あなたは夢中になります
yeah, I'm amazing
ええ、私は素晴らしいです
I'm amazing
私はすごいです
amazing
すばらしい
yeah, she's my goatress
ええ、彼女は私のヤトレスです
yeah
うん
she's my goatress
彼女は私のヤトレスです
yeah, yeah, she's my wife
ええ、ええ、彼女は私の妻です
goatress
ヤチレス
wife goatress
妻ヤトレス
goatress
ヤチレス
I don't know how poor you are
あなたがどれほど貧しいかわかりません
goddess
女神
yeah, kimoi
ええ、
yeah, she's my goddess
ええ、彼女は私の女神です
why
なぜ
oh my
ああ
oh my god
何てことだ
I feel like a son
私は息子のように感じます
oh my god
何てことだ
I'm sorry
ごめんなさい
yes
はい
it's okay
大丈夫
it's okay, it's no problem
大丈夫です、問題ありません
yeah, okay
ええ、わかりました